foodeliciouz.com 2019-04-01

# Privacy Policy – Foodeliciouz

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Foodeliciouz.com collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a “User”) of the www.Foodeliciouz.com website (“Site”). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by Foodeliciouz.com

## Personal identification information.

We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways in connection with activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.

## Non-personal identification information

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service provider’s utilized and other similar information.

## Web browser cookies

Our Site may use “cookies” to enhance User experience. User’s web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

## How we use collected information

Foodeliciouz.com may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes:  
– To improve customer service  
Information you provide helps us respond to your customer service requests and support needs more efficiently.

## How we protect your information

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.

## Sharing your personal information

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.

When we process your personal data within Foodeliciouz this may involve processing and transferring your data outside the European Economic Area (EEA), which includes all EU member states plus Iceland, Liechtenstein and Norway.

When your data is transferred outside the EEA we take steps to make sure it has the same level of protection as it would have in the EEA. Our agreements with third parties make clear the standards we expect of them in order to safeguard your information and your legal rights.

## Google Adsense

Some of the ads may be served by Google. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to Users based on their visit to our Site and other sites on the Internet. DART uses “non personally identifiable information” and does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, etc. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

## Right to withdraw consent

If we are processing your personal data on the basis of your consent, you can withdraw your consent at any time.

## Right to request transfer

You have the right to ask us to transfer your personal data to you, or to a third party. This right applies only to automated information you gave us consent to use, or where we used the information to perform a contract with you.

## How to exercise your rights

To exercise your rights you can contact us via our contact page. As a security measure we will ask you to verify your identity. If a third party is making a request on your behalf we will ask them to prove that they have your permission to act for you.

We may contact you to ask you for further information to help you exercise your legal rights, or to speed up our response. We will try to respond to requests within one month and we will let you know if we need to take longer. We may have an overriding lawful basis for processing your personal data, or certain exemptions may apply. If we refuse your request we will explain why.

## Complaints

You have the right to complain about data privacy matters to the Information Commissioner’s Office (www.ico.org.uk), or the relevant data protection regulator in your country of residence. We invite you to raise your concerns with us first, so that we can try to resolve them.

## Changes to this privacy policy

Foodeliciouz.com has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

## Your acceptance of these terms

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

 **Contacting us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please **[contact us](http://foodeliciouz.com/contact-us/).**

Additions: 30.05.2018

Table of contents

  * Responsible organization
  * Cookies
  * Third parties and opt-out
  * Other / unforeseen Cookies
  * Your rights with regards to your data
  * Modifications and contact

RESPONSIBLE ORGANIZATION

Responsible organization (also “person responsible“) is Yieldlove GmbH, Kehrwieder 9, 20457 Hamburg, following “Yieldlove” or “we” respectively “us”.

COOKIES

What are cookies?

Cookies are small text files that are sent when you visit a website and stored in the browser of the user. If the corresponding Internet page is retrieved, the browser of the user sends back the content of the cookies and thus enables recognition of the user. Certain cookies are automatically deleted after the end of the browser session (so-called session cookies), others are stored for a predetermined time or permanently in the user’s browser and then delete themselves (so-called temporary or permanent cookies)

What data is stored in the cookies?

In cookies, no personal data is stored, but only an online identifier.

How can you prevent the use of cookies or delete cookies?

You can deactivate the storage of cookies via your browser settings and delete already stored cookies at any time in your browser (see the section “Technical notes”). Please note, however, that this online offering without cookies may not work or may only work to a limited extent.

Please note, furthermore, that contradictions against the creation of usage profiles partly work through a so-called “opt-out cookie”. If you delete all cookies, a contradiction may therefore no longer be taken into account and must be collected again by you.

What cookies do we use?

Analysis cookies

We use analysis cookies in order to be able to record the usage behavior (eg clicked advertising banners, visited sub-pages, made search queries) of our users and to evaluate them in statistical form.

Advertising cookies

We also use cookies for promotional purposes. Usage profiles created using these cookies (eg, clicked banner ads, visited subpages, requested search queries) are used by us to show you advertisements or offers that are tailored to your interests (“interest-based advertising”).

Advertising cookies of third parties

We also allow other companies to collect our users’ data through advertising cookies. This allows us and third parties to provide users of our online service with interest-based advertising based on an analysis of their usage behavior (eg, clicked banner ads, visited subpages, requested search queries), and not limited to our online offerings.

Yieldlove delivers advertising banners on behalf of its customers. All our banners use cookies. We place these banners on third-party websites, such as a news page, with the help of third-party providers.

For diagnostic purposes, troubleshooting, and detecting fraudulent behavior, we collect user information in cookies using our 6-month lifecycle. The captured user information includes user agent, device, HTTP referrer and the IP. This data is not retained for more than 7 days.

Yieldlove takes reasonable steps to protect any information we process from misuse, loss, unauthorized access, modification or notification. We take physical, electronic and procedural security measures to protect the data we process. By doing so, we restrict access to this information to authorized employees.

For the cookies that our third-party advertisers place for advertising purposes, we refer to the disclaimers that they have provided on the topic on their own websites. Note that we can only refer to these disclaimers, as they change regularly and Yieldlove has no control over them.

THIRD PARTIES AND OPT-OUT

A central contradiction possibility for different third-party suppliers in particular US-companies is also attainable under the following link: optout.networkadvertising.org But you can also opt-out separately for each company we work with. Responsible for the data collection and for the delivery of interest based-based online advertising are the following companies on behalf of Yieldlove GmbH:

 _4w Marketplace_

4w Marketplace (www.4wmarketplace.com) uses technologies, to show interest-based advertising to you. Provider of 4w Marketplace is 4w Marketplace srl located in Fisciano (Salerno) – 84084 in Via Giovanni Paolo II n.100. In case you would like to prevent 4w Marketplace from gathering anonymised data you can do so by using the opt-out link below. This Opt-out cookie deletes all gathered information until now and prevents it from collecting any information in the future.

Privacy policy: <http://www.4wmarketplace.com/privacy/>

Opt-out: <http://www.youronlinechoices.com/it/le-tue-scelte>

_Adform_

Adform (www.adform.com) uses technologies, to show interest-based advertising to you. Provider of Adform is Adform located in Wildersgade 10B, 1, 1408 Copenhagen, Denmark. In case you would like to prevent Adform from gathering anonymised data you can do so by using the opt-out link below. This Opt-out cookie deletes all gathered information until now and prevents it from collecting any information in the future.

Privacy policy: <https://site.adform.com/privacy-policy-opt-out/>

Opt-out: <https://site.adform.com/privacy-policy-opt-out/>

_Amazon_

Amazon (https://www.aps.amazon.com) uses technologies, to show interest-based advertising to you. Provider of Amazon publisher services is Amazon publisher services located in Washington – 410 Terry Ave. North, Seattle, WA 98109-5210. In case you would like to prevent Amazon publisher services from gathering anonymised data you can do so by using the opt-out link below. This Opt-out cookie deletes all gathered information until now and prevents it from collecting any information in the future.

Privacy policy: [https://www.amazon.com/gp/help/customer/display.html/ref=hp_left_sib?ie=UTF8&nodeId=468496](https://www.amazon.com/gp/help/customer/display.html/ref=hp_left_sib?ie=UTF8&nodeId=468496)

Opt-out: <https://www.amazon.com/adprefs/ref=hp_468496_advertisingpref2>

_AppNexus_

AppNexus (https://www.appnexus.com) uses technologies, to show interest-based advertising to you. Provider of AppNexus is AppNexus Group located in in New York – 28 W. 23rd  Street, New York, New York, 10010. In case you would like to prevent Appnexus from gathering anonymised data you can do so by using the opt-out link below. This Opt-out cookie deletes all gathered information until now and prevents it from collecting any information in the future.

Privacy policy: https://www.appnexus.com/en/company/privacy-policy

Opt-out: https://www.appnexus.com/en/company/platform-privacy-policy#choices

 _Conversant_

Conversant (https://www.conversantmedia.com) uses technologies, to show interest-based advertising to you. Provider of Conversant is Conversant inc. located in in Chicago (IL) – 101 North Wacker, 23rd  Floor Chicago, IL 60606. In case you would like to prevent Conversant from gathering anonymised data you can do so by using the opt-out link below. This Opt-out cookie deletes all gathered information until now and prevents it from collecting any information in the future.

Privacy policy: <http://www.conversantmedia.com/legal/privacy>

Opt-out: http://optout.conversantmedia.com/

 _Criteo_

Criteo (https://www.criteo.com) uses technologies, to show interest-based advertising to you. Provider of Criteo is Criteo located in Paris – 32 Rue Blanche – 75009 Paris – France. In case you would like to prevent Criteo from gathering anonymised data you can do so by using the opt-out link below. This Opt-out cookie deletes all gathered information until now and prevents it from collecting any information in the future.

Privacy policy: http://www.criteo.com/privacy/

Opt-out: https://www.criteo.com/privacy/

District M

District M (https://districtm.net) uses technologies, to show interest-based advertising to you. Provider of District M is District M located in Montreal – 5455 Gaspe Ave #730, Montreal, QC H2T 3B3, Canada. In case you would like to prevent District M from gathering anonymised data you can do so by using the opt-out link below. This Opt-out cookie deletes all gathered information until now and prevents it from collecting any information in the future.

Privacy policy: <https://districtm.net/en/page/platforms-data-and-privacy-policy/>

Opt-out: <https://cdn.districtm.ca/optout.html>

Doubleclick

Doubleclick (www.doubleclickbygoogle.com) uses technologies, to show interest-based advertising to you. Provider of Doubleclick is Google located in Ireland Limited, Gordon House, Barrow St Dublin 4 Ireland. In case you would like to prevent Doubleclick from gathering anonymised data you can do so by using the opt-out link below. This Opt-out cookie deletes all gathered information until now and prevents it from collecting any information in the future.

Privacy policy: http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/

Opt-out: <https://adssettings.google.com/authenticated?hl=en>

Facebook

Facebook (www.facebook.com) uses technologies, to show interest-based advertising to you. Provider of Facebook is Facebook Inc., located in 1601 S. California Ave, Palo Alto, CA 94304, USA. In case you would like to prevent Facebook from gathering anonymised data you can do so by using the opt-out link below. This Opt-out cookie deletes all gathered information until now and prevents it from collecting any information in the future.

Privacy policy: www.facebook.com/full_data_use_policy

Opt-out: www.facebook.com/ads/preferences

Indexexchange

Indexexchange (www.indexexchange.com) uses technologies, to show interest-based advertising to you. Provider of Indexexchange is Indexexchange located in New York – 20 W 22nd  St. Suite 1101, New York, NY 10010. In case you would like to prevent Indexexchange from gathering anonymised data you can do so by using the opt-out link below. This Opt-out cookie deletes all gathered information until now and prevents it from collecting any information in the future.

Privacy policy: <http://www.indexexchange.com/privacy/>

Opt-out: http://optout.networkadvertising.org/?c=1#!/

Media.net

Media.net (http://www.media.net/privacy-policy) uses technologies, to show interest-based advertising to you. Provider of Media.net is Media.net Advertising Ltd. located in Dubai – 107/108, DIC Building 5, Dubai Internet City, Dubai, 215028, United Arab Emirates. In case you would like to prevent Media.net from gathering anonymised data you can do so by using the opt-out link below. This Opt-out cookie deletes all gathered information until now and prevents it from collecting any information in the future.

Privacy policy: http://www.media.net/privacy-policy

Opt-out: <http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/>

_Oath_

Oath (https://www.oath.com/) uses technologies, to show interest-based advertising to you. Provider of Oath is Oath (EMEA) Limited located in Dublin – 5-7 Point Square, North Wall Quay. In case you would like to prevent Oath from gathering anonymised data you can do so by using the opt-out link below. This Opt-out cookie deletes all gathered information until now and prevents it from collecting any information in the future.

Privacy policy: <http://privacy.aol.com/>

Opt-out: https://aim.yahoo.com/aim/ie/en/optout/

OpenX

OpenX (https://www.OpenX.com) uses technologies, to show interest-based advertising to you. Provider of OpenX is OpenX located in Pasadena – 888 E Walnut St, 2nd Floor, Pasadena CA, 91101, USA. In case you would like to prevent OpenX from gathering anonymised data you can do so by using the opt-out link below. This Opt-out cookie deletes all gathered information until now and prevents it from collecting any information in the future.

Privacy policy: https://www.openx.com/de_de/privacy-policy/

Opt-out: <https://www.openx.com/legal/interest-based-advertising/>

Pubmatic

Pubmatic (https://www.pubmatic.com) uses technologies, to show interest-based advertising to you. Provider of Pubmatic is Pubmatic, Inc. located in Redwood City – 305 Main Street, First Floor, Redwood City, California 94063, USA. In case you would like to prevent Pubmatic from gathering anonymised data you can do so by using the opt-out link below. This Opt-out cookie deletes all gathered information until now and prevents it from collecting any information in the future.

Privacy policy: https://www.openx.com/de_de/privacy-policy/

Opt-out: https://pubmatic.com/legal/opt-out/

Pulsepoint

Pulsepoint (https://www.pulsepoint.com) uses technologies, to show interest-based advertising to you. Provider of Pulsepoint is Pulsepoint, Inc. located in New York – 360 Madison Avenue, 14th Floor, New York, NY 10017. In case you would like to prevent Pulsepoint from gathering anonymised data you can do so by using the opt-out link below. This Opt-out cookie deletes all gathered information until now and prevents it from collecting any information in the future.

Privacy policy: <https://www.pulsepoint.com/privacy-policy>

Opt-out: http://optout.networkadvertising.org/?c=1#!/

Reachnet

Reachnet (https://www.reachnet.de) uses technologies, to show interest-based advertising to you. Provider of Reachnet is Reachnet DE Ltd. located in Hamburg – Grindelallee 41, D-20146 Hamburg. In case you would like to prevent Reachnet from gathering anonymised data you can do so by using the opt-out link below. This Opt-out cookie deletes all gathered information until now and prevents it from collecting any information in the future.

Privacy policy: http://www.reachnet.de/unternehmen/agb.html

Opt-out: [https://adfarm1.adition.com/opt?m=optout&n=73](https://adfarm1.adition.com/opt?m=optout&n=73)

Rubicon Project

Rubicon Project (https://www.rubiconproject.com) uses technologies, to show interest-based advertising to you. Provider of Rubicon Project is Rubicon Project, inc. located in Playa Vista – 12181 Bluff Creek Drive, 4th Floor, Playa Vista, CA 90094, USA. In case you would like to prevent Rubicon Project from gathering anonymised data you can do so by using the opt-out link below. This Opt-out cookie deletes all gathered information until now and prevents it from collecting any information in the future.

Privacy policy: http://www.rubiconproject.com/privacy-policy/

Opt-out: <https://rubiconproject.com/privacy/consumer-online-profile-and-opt-out/>

Primis

Primis (https://www.primis.tech) uses technologies, to show interest-based advertising to you. Provider of Primis is Primis LTD located in 622 Third avenue, McCann New York House 10017 New York City, USA. In case you would like to prevent Primis from gathering anonymised data you can do so by using the opt-out link below. This Opt-out cookie deletes all gathered information until now and prevents it from collecting any information in the future.

Privacy policy: https://www.primis.tech/wp-content/uploads/2018/02/primisPrivacyPolicy2018.pdf

Opt-out: https://web.archive.org/web/20180116234711/http:/live.sekindo.com/utils/cookieOptOut.php

Smaato

Smaato (https://www.smaato.com) uses technologies, to show interest-based advertising to you. Provider of Smaato is Smaato Ad Services located in Hamburg – Valentinskamp 70, Emporio, 20355 Hamburg, Germany. In case you would like to prevent Smaato from gathering anonymised data you can do so by using the opt-out link below. This Opt-out cookie deletes all gathered information until now and prevents it from collecting any information in the future.

Privacy policy: <https://www.smaato.com/privacy/>

Opt-out: [http://www.youronlinechoices.eu](https://www.youronlinechoices.eu/)

SmartAdserver

SmartAdserver (https://www.smartadserver.com) uses technologies, to show interest-based advertising to you. Provider of SmartAdserver is SmartAdserver located in Paris – 66 Rue de la Chaussée d´Antin, 75009 Paris, France. In case you would like to prevent SmartAdserver from gathering anonymised data you can do so by using the opt-out link below. This Opt-out cookie deletes all gathered information until now and prevents it from collecting any information in the future.

Privacy policy: http://smartadserver.com/company/privacy-policy/

Opt-out: http://www.smartadserver.com/diffx/optout/IABOptout.aspx

Sovrn

Sovrn (https://www.sovrn.com) uses technologies, to show interest-based advertising to you. Provider of Sovrn is Sovrn Holdings, Inc. located in Boulder – 5541 Central Avenue, Boulder, CO 80301. In case you would like to prevent Sovrn from gathering anonymised data you can do so by using the opt-out link below. This Opt-out cookie deletes all gathered information until now and prevents it from collecting any information in the future.

Privacy policy: <https://www.sovrn.com/privacy-policy-eu/>

Opt-out: https://info.evidon.com/pub_info/15620?v=1&nt=0&nw=false

 _Ströer SSP_

Ströer SSP (https://www.adscale.de) uses technologies, to show interest-based advertising to you. Provider of Ströer SSP is Ströer media Deutschland GmbH located in Köln – 50999 Köln, Ströer-Allee 1. In case you would like to prevent Adscale from gathering anonymised data you can do so by using the opt-out link below. This Opt-out cookie deletes all gathered information until now and prevents it from collecting any information in the future.

Privacy policy: <http://www.adscale.de/datenschutz>

Opt-out: ih.adscale.de/adscale-ih/oo

Twiago

Twiago (https://www.twiago.com) uses technologies, to show interest-based advertising to you. Provider of Twiago is Twiago located in Köln – Gustav-Heinemann-Ufer 72b, 50968 Köln. In case you would like to prevent Twiago from gathering anonymised data you can do so by using the opt-out link below. This Opt-out cookie deletes all gathered information until now and prevents it from collecting any information in the future.

Privacy policy: http://www.twiago.com/datenschutz/

Opt-out: http://control.twiago.com/privacy.php?lang=0

Mopub

Mopub (https://www.mopub.com) uses technologies, to show interest-based advertising to you. Provider of Mopub is Twitter, Inc. located in San Francisco – 1355 Market Street, Suite 900, San Francisco, Ca 94103. In case you would like to prevent Moppub from gathering anonymised data you can do so by using the opt-out link below. This Opt-out cookie deletes all gathered information until now and prevents it from collecting any information in the future.

Privacy policy: https://www.mopub.com/legal/privacy/

Opt-out: https://www.mopub.com/legal/privacy/

Inmobi

Inmobi (https://www.inmobi.com) uses technologies, to show interest-based advertising to you. Provider of Inmobi is Inmobi Pte Ltd located in Bangalore – Embassy Tech Square, Kadubeesanahalli Village Outer Ring Road, Varthur Hobli, Bangalore 560103. In case you would like to prevent Inmobi from gathering anonymised data you can do so by using the opt-out link below. This Opt-out cookie deletes all gathered information until now and prevents it from collecting any information in the future.

Privacy policy: <https://www.inmobi.com/privacy-policy/>

Opt-out: https://www.inmobi.com/page/opt-out/

OTHER / UNFORESEEN COOKIES

Due to the way in which Internet and websites work, it is possible that we do not always have oversight into the cookies that are placed through our banners by third parties. This is particularly the case when our banners contain embedded elements such as texts, documents, images or film clips that are stored by another party, but that are shown on, in or through our banners.

Should you encounter cookies on this website that fall into this category which we have not mentioned above, please let us know or contact the third party directly and ask which cookies they have placed, what the reason for this is, what the lifetime of the cookie is and in what way they have safeguarded your privacy.

YOUR RIGHTS WITH REGARDS TO YOUR DATA

Yieldlove does not view the banner advertising data it uses as personal data under the applicable law. Likewise, we do not collect or process sensitive personal data such as data on racial or ethnic origin, political opinions, religious or philosophical beliefs, trade union membership, health, or sex life. We also do not knowingly collect data from children under the age of 12.

However, if you want to correct, update or delete the banner advertising data we have, or if you would like to correct, update or delete the personal data that you have provided to us via the contact form on our homepage, you can contact us by e-mail at [privacy@yieldlove.com](mailto:privacy@yieldlove.com).

EDAA

We participate in the European Digital Advertising Alliance (EDAA) self-regulatory programs and adhere to the [EDAA Principles for Online Behavioral Advertising](http://www.edaa.eu/european-principles/). EDAA principally acts as the central licensing body for the OBA Icon and provides technical means for consumers to exercise transparency and control over OBA through the youronlinechoices.eu online consumer choice platform. EDAA is governed by EU-level organisations which make up the value chain of OBA within Europe and acts to ensure European consistency in approach. Click [here](http://www.edaa.eu/) to learn more about the EDAA.

MODIFICATIONS AND CONTACT

We will, on occasion need to adapt these statements. For instance, if we modify our website or if the rules governing cookies or privacy change. We or our partners may always modify the content of the statements and the cookies that are stated without prior warning. Please refer back to this web page to see the latest version.

In case you have any questions and/or comments, or wish to make a complaint, please contact us by e-mail at [privacy@yieldlove.com](mailto:privacy@yieldlove.com) or by writing to:

Yieldlove GmbH  
Kehrwieder 9  
20457 Hamburg  
Germany
